let multiplicationquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 10 x 6",
        AnswerA: "40",
        AnswerB: "50",
        AnswerC: "60",
        AnswerD: "70",
        correctAnswer: "60",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 6",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "43",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "45",
        correctAnswer: "42",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 3 x 9",
        AnswerA: "23",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 8 x 6",
        AnswerA: "44",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "48",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "48",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 3 x 3",
        AnswerA: "7",
        AnswerB: "8",
        AnswerC: "9",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 4",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "32",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 6 x 9",
        AnswerA: "52",
        AnswerB: "54",
        AnswerC: "56",
        AnswerD: "58",
        correctAnswer: "54",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 5 x 7",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "39",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "35",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 5 x 9",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "47",
        AnswerC: "49",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "45",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 5 x 8",
        AnswerA: "40",
        AnswerB: "42",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 5 x 6",
        AnswerA: "28",
        AnswerB: "30",
        AnswerC: "32",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 x 3",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "34",
        AnswerC: "36",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 x 4",
        AnswerA: "48",
        AnswerB: "50",
        AnswerC: "52",
        AnswerD: "54",
        correctAnswer: "52",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 3 x 11",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "33",
        AnswerC: "35",
        AnswerD: "37",
        correctAnswer: "33",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 2 x 12",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 10 x 3",
        AnswerA: "20",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 x 3",
        AnswerA: "67",
        AnswerB: "68",
        AnswerC: "69",
        AnswerD: "71",
        correctAnswer: "69",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 x 5",
        AnswerA: "115",
        AnswerB: "120",
        AnswerC: "125",
        AnswerD: "130",
        correctAnswer: "125",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 10 x 11",
        AnswerA: "105",
        AnswerB: "110",
        AnswerC: "115",
        AnswerD: "120",
        correctAnswer: "110",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 x 12",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "144",
        AnswerC: "146",
        AnswerD: "148",
        correctAnswer: "144",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 11 x 11",
        AnswerA: "121",
        AnswerB: "122",
        AnswerC: "123",
        AnswerD: "124",
        correctAnswer: "121",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 x 13",
        AnswerA: "163",
        AnswerB: "165",
        AnswerC: "167",
        AnswerD: "169",
        correctAnswer: "169",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 11 x 8",
        AnswerA: "86",
        AnswerB: "87",
        AnswerC: "88",
        AnswerD: "89",
        correctAnswer: "88",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 x 9",
        AnswerA: "153",
        AnswerB: "154",
        AnswerC: "156",
        AnswerD: "157",
        correctAnswer: "153",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 x 8",
        AnswerA: "72",
        AnswerB: "73",
        AnswerC: "74",
        AnswerD: "76",
        correctAnswer: "72",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 8",
        AnswerA: "54",
        AnswerB: "56",
        AnswerC: "57",
        AnswerD: "58",
        correctAnswer: "56",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 8 x 8",
        AnswerA: "62",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 x 9",
        AnswerA: "79",
        AnswerB: "81",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "85",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 x 12",
        AnswerA: "104",
        AnswerB: "106",
        AnswerC: "107",
        AnswerD: "108",
        correctAnswer: "108",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 16 x 7",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "114",
        AnswerC: "116",
        AnswerD: "118",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 16 x 6",
        AnswerA: "96",
        AnswerB: "97",
        AnswerC: "98",
        AnswerD: "99",
        correctAnswer: "96",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 x 5",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "80",
        AnswerC: "85",
        AnswerD: "90",
        correctAnswer: "85",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 x 4",
        AnswerA: "72",
        AnswerB: "74",
        AnswerC: "76",
        AnswerD: "78",
        correctAnswer: "72",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 6",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "114",
        AnswerC: "116",
        AnswerD: "118",
        correctAnswer: "114",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 14 x 11",
        AnswerA: "152",
        AnswerB: "154",
        AnswerC: "156",
        AnswerD: "158",
        correctAnswer: "154",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 33 x 3",
        AnswerA: "95",
        AnswerB: "96",
        AnswerC: "97",
        AnswerD: "99",
        correctAnswer: "99",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 x 4",
        AnswerA: "92",
        AnswerB: "94",
        AnswerC: "96",
        AnswerD: "98",
        correctAnswer: "96",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 x 5",
        AnswerA: "55",
        AnswerB: "60",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "70",
        correctAnswer: "65",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 5",
        AnswerA: "90",
        AnswerB: "91",
        AnswerC: "93",
        AnswerD: "95",
        correctAnswer: "95",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 x 4",
        AnswerA: "102",
        AnswerB: "104",
        AnswerC: "106",
        AnswerD: "108",
        correctAnswer: "108",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 21 x 8",
        AnswerA: "162",
        AnswerB: "164",
        AnswerC: "166",
        AnswerD: "168",
        correctAnswer: "168",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 x 12",
        AnswerA: "154",
        AnswerB: "156",
        AnswerC: "158",
        AnswerD: "160",
        correctAnswer: "156",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 x 15",
        AnswerA: "175",
        AnswerB: "180",
        AnswerC: "185",
        AnswerD: "190",
        correctAnswer: "180",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 x 6",
        AnswerA: "80",
        AnswerB: "85",
        AnswerC: "90",
        AnswerD: "95",
        correctAnswer: "90",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 14 x 7",
        AnswerA: "92",
        AnswerB: "94",
        AnswerC: "96",
        AnswerD: "98",
        correctAnswer: "98",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 14 x 6",
        AnswerA: "82",
        AnswerB: "84",
        AnswerC: "86",
        AnswerD: "88",
        correctAnswer: "84",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 16 x 5",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "80",
        AnswerC: "85",
        AnswerD: "90",
        correctAnswer: "80",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 16 x 4",
        AnswerA: "62",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 16 x 19",
        AnswerA: "302",
        AnswerB: "304",
        AnswerC: "306",
        AnswerD: "308",
        correctAnswer: "304",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 x 30",
        AnswerA: "260",
        AnswerB: "270",
        AnswerC: "280",
        AnswerD: "290",
        correctAnswer: "270",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 25",
        AnswerA: "165",
        AnswerB: "170",
        AnswerC: "175",
        AnswerD: "180",
        correctAnswer: "175",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 8 x 22",
        AnswerA: "173",
        AnswerB: "174",
        AnswerC: "175",
        AnswerD: "176",
        correctAnswer: "176",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 34 x 7",
        AnswerA: "234",
        AnswerB: "236",
        AnswerC: "237",
        AnswerD: "238",
        correctAnswer: "238",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 29 x 8",
        AnswerA: "229",
        AnswerB: "231",
        AnswerC: "232",
        AnswerD: "233",
        correctAnswer: "232",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 x 8",
        AnswerA: "191",
        AnswerB: "192",
        AnswerC: "193",
        AnswerD: "194",
        correctAnswer: "192",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 x 12",
        AnswerA: "202",
        AnswerB: "203",
        AnswerC: "204",
        AnswerD: "205",
        correctAnswer: "204",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 14",
        AnswerA: "264",
        AnswerB: "266",
        AnswerC: "267",
        AnswerD: "268",
        correctAnswer: "266",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 44 x 9",
        AnswerA: "392",
        AnswerB: "394",
        AnswerC: "396",
        AnswerD: "398",
        correctAnswer: "396",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 33 x 8",
        AnswerA: "262",
        AnswerB: "264",
        AnswerC: "266",
        AnswerD: "268",
        correctAnswer: "264",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 + 6",
        AnswerA: "282",
        AnswerB: "284",
        AnswerC: "286",
        AnswerD: "288",
        correctAnswer: "288",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 x 12",
        AnswerA: "311",
        AnswerB: "312",
        AnswerC: "313",
        AnswerD: "314",
        correctAnswer: "312",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 x 11",
        AnswerA: "192",
        AnswerB: "194",
        AnswerC: "196",
        AnswerD: "198",
        correctAnswer: "198",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 12",
        AnswerA: "225",
        AnswerB: "226",
        AnswerC: "227",
        AnswerD: "228",
        correctAnswer: "228",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 72",
        AnswerA: "502",
        AnswerB: "504",
        AnswerC: "506",
        AnswerD: "508",
        correctAnswer: "504",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 78 x 9",
        AnswerA: "702",
        AnswerB: "704",
        AnswerC: "706",
        AnswerD: "708",
        correctAnswer: "702",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 x 9",
        AnswerA: "422",
        AnswerB: "423",
        AnswerC: "424",
        AnswerD: "425",
        correctAnswer: "423",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 14 x 18",
        AnswerA: "252",
        AnswerB: "253",
        AnswerC: "254",
        AnswerD: "255",
        correctAnswer: "252",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 x 17",
        AnswerA: "321",
        AnswerB: "322",
        AnswerC: "323",
        AnswerD: "324",
        correctAnswer: "323",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 x 20",
        AnswerA: "290",
        AnswerB: "300",
        AnswerC: "305",
        AnswerD: "310",
        correctAnswer: "300",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 54 x 9",
        AnswerA: "482",
        AnswerB: "483",
        AnswerC: "484",
        AnswerD: "486",
        correctAnswer: "486",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 81 x 9",
        AnswerA: "726",
        AnswerB: "727",
        AnswerC: "729",
        AnswerD: "731",
        correctAnswer: "729",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 62 x 6",
        AnswerA: "672",
        AnswerB: "673",
        AnswerC: "674",
        AnswerD: "676",
        correctAnswer: "672",
    },
]